



RZ-D1A50b gali no 5 Mahavir enclave New Delhi 110045



7503603463,9267916020



Arvindsingh171997@gm ail.com

Languages

English

Hindi

Arvind Singh Yadav

A core healthcare domain professional with 4.3 years of experience in US healthcare RCM, obtain a position within the Company where I can utilize my management skills and experience in Process Management, quality assurance and training. My emphasis is on learning and value addition and to serve the organization with our dedication, honesty and to the best of my abilities.

WORK EXPERIENCE

**Assistant team leader, Vocis LLC. Delhi, Delhi

Feb. 2022 - Present

** Ensuring SLA is met with respect to the Revenue, Productivity & Quality.

Processing Client requests, Complaints and Concerns on a priority basis.

- ** Administer performance management by diagnosing improvement opportunities, providing effective feedback, coaching, training and corrective action plans.
- ** Helps the Team leader in Setting the production targets on a monthly/Quarterly basis and achieving them.
- ** Preparing daily workloads for staff & co-coordinating the daily allocation of work. And monthly reports and attendance.
- ** Handling the team of 6 member also assist team leader for other projects.
- ** Dealing with and resolving problems and issues which arise.
- ** Follow up with the payer for obtaining status of claims through calls and websites Mostly 90+ ageing Claims & appeals.

**Senior executive, Vocis LLC. Delhi, Delhi May. 2020 - Jan. 2022

- ** Analyze the outstanding accounts on the ATB (Aged Trial Balance) and identify transactions requiring follow-up with Insurance.
- ** Provided training to the new hires. Mentoring and training up junior and new associates
- ** Resolved issues and recommended actions based on production and compliance reports.



- **Analyst, R1rcm. Gurugram, Haryana Sep. 2019 Apr. 2020
- **Accounts Receivable Follow up on all denials, including appeals.
- ** Work on aging reports and special projects.
- ** Worked on commercial client for the state of Illinois.

Executive, Teleperformance. Gurugram, Haryana May. 2018 - Aug. 2019

- ** Billing Charges based on the information provided by the providers of US Hospitals for their patients.
- ** Payment and denials projects and DME work.

Education

- **Shiv Vani model se. Sec. School, Delhi, Dwarka new Delhi
 High School Diploma, Class 12
- **Dyal Singh college, Delhi, Delhi Bachelor of Arts, Political science, Jul. 2016

Awards

- **Emerging leader of the month.
- **Several times Star performance of the month
- **Best Performer of the Quarter.

Accomplishments

- ** Was awarded Rising Star for performing well, post RCM training.
- ** Trained the new team on physician.
- ** Was awarded Extra Miler, Star Quality and Star Performer at the same quarter during my tenure.
- ** Handled several sub process within the project successfully and have groomed team members.